nexusrv.com 2011-11-30

# NeXus RV Privacy Policy | NeXus RV

## **Privacy Policy**

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter   
your name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Like most websites, we use cookies and/or web beacons to enhance   
your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website.   
Please refer to the 'do we use cookies?' section below for information   
about cookies and how we use them.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be   
used in one of the following ways:

**The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you  
information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving   
occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.**

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails,   
we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers   
to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow)   
that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser   
and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and   
site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties   
your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties   
who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you,   
so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information   
when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies,   
or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally   
identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties   
for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products   
or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and   
independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content   
and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site   
and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions   
to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act.   
We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act),   
we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age.   
Our website, products and services are all directed to people   
who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through   
our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [privacy policy](http://www.nexusrv.com/privacypolicy.php).

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

This policy was last modified on August 3, 2011 

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

<http://www.nexusrv.com/contact.php>
